<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-12T20:37:20+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Beacon</title><subtitle>The Beacon is MCI's newspaper.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">🥓 Exclusive Facts About Ed Sheeran</title><link href="/2021/04/ed_sheeran.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 Exclusive Facts About Ed Sheeran" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/ed_sheeran</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/ed_sheeran.html">&lt;p&gt;Extra! Extra! Read all about it! On this momentous day, I thought I
would take the time to raise awareness for a small local artist named Ed
Sheeran. His hair is incredible, and his music is good too. Myself,
along with world-renowned researchers, conducted a thorough
investigation into his life, feelings, emotions, and actions. We dove
deep, and found many exclusive facts about him. So, enjoy these 12
absolutely true and deeply personal facts about Ed Sheeran:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’s in love with the shape of you&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’s on his way, driving at 90 down those country lanes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He could fall or he could fly here in your aeroplane&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ed’s going to pick up the pieces and build a lego house, because he
knows that when things go wrong, he can knock it down&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’s in love with his pretty little galway girl&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ed enjoys jumping in the water, and going south of the border&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He doesn’t think he fits in at this party since, you and him, aren’t
beautiful people&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’ll hold on tighter till the afterglow&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ed keeps his love in a photograph, and makes memories for himself&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’s thinking ‘bout how people fall in love in mysterious ways&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’s been a liar, been a cheat, been a lover, been a thief&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;He’s telling himself you’re happier, aren’t you?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research Contributors: Ella Wong, Katie Daynyko-Pavlov, Caroline
Miszkiel, Anupra Chandran&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Credit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/24400573@N03/7456774820&quot;&gt;“Ed Sheeran - Hovefestivalen 2012”&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/24400573@N03&quot;&gt;NRK P3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>smahmud</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Extra! Extra! Read all about it! On this momentous day, I thought I would take the time to raise awareness for a small local artist named Ed Sheeran. His hair is incredible, and his music is good too. Myself, along with world-renowned researchers, conducted a thorough investigation into his life, feelings, emotions, and actions. We dove deep, and found many exclusive facts about him. So, enjoy these 12 absolutely true and deeply personal facts about Ed Sheeran:</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/ed_sheeran.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/ed_sheeran.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 The Reason MCI Doesn’t Have Windows</title><link href="/2021/04/mci_windows.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 The Reason MCI Doesn’t Have Windows" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/mci_windows</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/mci_windows.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey Bears! Regardless of how long you’ve been at MCI, you’ve definitely
noticed that our school lacks a significant thing: windows. We, at the
Beacon, recently came across ancient MCI history books, and discovered
the reason why our school doesn’t have windows. We feel that it is our
journalistic duty to share this information with you, so behold, the
true story of why MCI does not have windows. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MCI was designed in the 1960s by a man known as the Great Baron of
Martingrove, E.N. Closure. His family was of great wealth and status
here in Etobicoke, yet the Baron was the last living member. It’s
important to mention that the Baron’s family had a bitter rivalry with
the other resident affluent family, the Fenetres. The two families had
been disagreeing for centuries, ever since their great grandfathers got
into an argument about the true solution of 1+1. Their dispute resulted
in a violent cheese bread fight, but then ended with a group of geese
chasing them both away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baron wanted to build a school in his family’s name, to maintain
their legacy. He had many lavish plans for the school: great big
hallways, spacious lockers, adorned with beautiful school colours of
green and white, and most importantly, lots of glorious windows. The
Baron was just about to begin constructing this very school, when he
received the list of students who would be enrolling. All was in order,
until he saw one name at the very bottom of this list: Lisa Fenetre, the
youngest member of the rival Fenetre family. She would be attending
grade 9 at the Baron’s school. This sent the Baron into a fury, and due
to his blind rage towards the Fenetres, he completely scrapped all his
plans for the school. Most notably, he knew that the Fenetres loved
natural light and looking outside, so he decided not to put any windows
in any classrooms. They would only be in the stairwells and at the ends
of the hallways. He wanted Lisa’s school experience to be miserable, and
for her to spend countless hours in math class actually learning what
1+1 is, without distractions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days later, Lisa Fenetre’s father, Charles, got word of the
Baron’s punishing plans for Lisa and the school. He was outraged, and
went to visit the Baron’s house on a street that was, at the time,
called Summerton. The two had a long fight; one so brutal and cold that
it caused a chill throughout the street. Finally, the Baron couldn’t
tolerate the verbal insults any longer. He went inside his house, and
emerged minutes later with handfuls of Jerry’s hotdogs, which he began
throwing at Mr. Fenetre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Get out of here, get off my property! I’m going to build the most
enclosed school in all of Etobicoke!” shouted the Baron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And because of the sheer power of Jerry’s hotdogs, Mr. Fenetre was
forced to concede, and return to his own home. The Baron, now unopposed,
was free to proceed with his plans. He built his school of regular
hallways, decorated with dull brown and orange school colors, and no
windows. As desired, he named the school Martingrove, after his own
family’s title.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That year, Lisa Fenetre attended Martingrove in the fall. She, along
with the rest of her family, was repulsed by the lack of windows within
the classrooms. Lisa transferred to Richview three months into the
school year. She went on to live a good life, but never did learn what
1+1 actually equalled. (do you know?!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the triumph of building his school, yet unable to truly punish the
Fenetres, the Baron sadly died at the age of 81. He died due to
excessive consumption of cheese bread, while surrounded by his
collection of computers that never connect to the school wifi. The
Martingrove legacy lives on through his school, and all those who attend
it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On that note, we end the fascinating story of why MCI doesn’t have
windows. We hope you learned something valuable through this story, and
always remember the supremacy of Jerry’s hotdogs. Without them, our
school may not have existed!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Credit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/65448940@N00/14692276582&quot;&gt;“Window”&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/65448940@N00&quot;&gt;Matti Mattila&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>smahmud</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Hey Bears! Regardless of how long you’ve been at MCI, you’ve definitely noticed that our school lacks a significant thing: windows. We, at the Beacon, recently came across ancient MCI history books, and discovered the reason why our school doesn’t have windows. We feel that it is our journalistic duty to share this information with you, so behold, the true story of why MCI does not have windows. Enjoy!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/mci_windows.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/mci_windows.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 Tragedy Strikes Meatingrove CI</title><link href="/2021/04/meatingrove.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 Tragedy Strikes Meatingrove CI" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/meatingrove</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/meatingrove.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last week, a series of tragic events occurred, starting with the mysterious eye of Eveloin Rib. But don’t worry - there’s mutton to fret about.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It all started in Science, last Monday morning,” said the Grade Nine
student. “I was trying to pay attention, and then one of my eyes popped
out.” Eveloin Rib’s eye gracefully leapt from its socket, witnesses
recalled, at 9:07 A.M. on Monday, rolling out the door and into the
hallway. After pausing briefly to look out the window, it made its way
through the Science hallway and tumbled down the stairs, although my
sources do not specify when or how. The whole Science class spent the
morning searching for the rogue eye, with no luck, but at last, Rib’s
eye was found cooling off in a water fountain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like most of Eveloin’s classmates, Hamantha Mince was very relieved.
“I’m just glad Eveloin’s eye was found. It would be unsettling knowing
that a stray eyeball still roams the halls of Meatingrove. “Wouldn’t
that be so unsettling?” said Mince in our interview yesterday. Eveloin
is recovering in the hospital, and she will return to school by Monday.
On behalf of all members here at The Bacon, I am extremely relieved for
both Eveloin and her reunited eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if a runaway eye wasn’t enough for our school last week, The Bacon’s
super top-secret undisclosed headquarters were found ablaze on Tuesday,
with no one at the scene. Although no one was there, sources state that
a math test belonging to Grade Ten student Vee Ande was found
suspiciously close to the cause of the fire: a can of Spam ignited by
pyrokinetic powers. The Spam can appears to remain sealed and unchanged,
so if anyone is looking for a meaty snack during breaktime, The Bacon’s
super top-secret undisclosed headquarters are always open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vee Ande was found the day after in the parking lot, pointing at similar
cans of Spam and muttering to herself, “You meathead, it was just a
misteak,” as she lit them on fire. I’m not pointing any fingers here,
but I am. Thankfully, no one was injured, and the damage from the Spam
fire was minute. It’s safe to say that we avoided being smoked bacon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In international news, the distant relative of Grade Twelve student
Chuck Ram was knighted last week. Chuck’s recount of how he and Sir
Alexhamder Loin OBE are related was a convoluted mess to listen to, but
I will take his word for it. Sir Loin entered knighthood on the 27th of
March at Buckingham Palace, being knighted Officer of the Most Excellent
Order of the Brifish Empire by Queen Elizabeef II, for global
contributions in the field of Physribs. Loin gave a very tender and
heartwarming speech afterwards, followed by a lovely performance of “I
Wanna Hold Your Ham’’ by The Beefles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week was certainly filled with mayham, but we are just happy
everyone is safe and sound.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Credit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/66323260@N04/6994994306&quot;&gt;“Zombie Eyeball”&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/66323260@N04&quot;&gt;Kelly’s Kustom Pinstriping&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sxiang</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Last week, a series of tragic events occurred, starting with the mysterious eye of Eveloin Rib. But don’t worry - there’s mutton to fret about.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/meatingrove.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/meatingrove.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 Meghan Markle Breathes, British Tabloids Outraged</title><link href="/2021/04/meghan_markle.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 Meghan Markle Breathes, British Tabloids Outraged" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/meghan_markle</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/meghan_markle.html">&lt;p&gt;Meghan Markle has been a source of scandal in the British tabloids,
upending many longstanding royal traditions. Among her alleged crimes
are being multiracial, being a woman, being American, having parents,
and existing. Yet her landmark Oprah interview in March led to
groundbreaking journalists at Mail on Sunday discovering something far
more nefarious about the Duchess of Sussex - her breathing during the
interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We watched this video clip maybe a hundred times,” said bleary-eyed
intern Leah Wimbleton. “We noticed that Markle displays a concerning
need for oxygen. See here, how she breathes between words? There’s
something fishy going on.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Self-described mature individual Piers Morgan was quick to offer his
input on the shocking behaviour. “At the ten-minute mark, Meghan
breathes for nine seconds. The same number of letters in Voldemort’s
name. Coincidence? I think not. It’s obvious, Meghan Markle is declaring
her support for Death Eaters.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;QAnon fundraiser and self-proclaimed “clown entrepreneur” David Jones
had his own take on the story. “I’ve heard rumours that Darth Vader also
breathes. I think there’s more connections between Markle and the Sith
then the fake news media would lead you to believe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Markle’s breathing has also been linked to an avocado shortage in South
America, and higher infant mortality rates, according to Leslie Wilbur.
“I saw it on Facebook,” she said. “Who does she think she is, taking the
precious breathing air that could go to children and babies? I don’t
think that climate change is real, or anything, but Meghan’s breathing
sure does cause a lot of CO2 emissions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At press time, Meghan Markle’s breathing was also linked to COVID-19,
the fall of the Roman Empire, and multiple Arkham Asylum breakouts in
Gotham.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Credit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://commons.wikimedia.org/w/index.php?curid=65635766&quot;&gt;“File:Prince Harry and Meghan Markle.jpg”&lt;/a&gt; by Mark Jones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>mhutzul</name></author><category term="articles" /><category term="sticky" /><summary type="html">Meghan Markle has been a source of scandal in the British tabloids, upending many longstanding royal traditions. Among her alleged crimes are being multiracial, being a woman, being American, having parents, and existing. Yet her landmark Oprah interview in March led to groundbreaking journalists at Mail on Sunday discovering something far more nefarious about the Duchess of Sussex - her breathing during the interview.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/meghan_markle.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/meghan_markle.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 BREAKING NEWS: NEW VIRUS HAS BEEN DISCOVERED AND HAS INFECTED OVER 1,000,000 PEOPLE</title><link href="/2021/04/new_virus.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 BREAKING NEWS: NEW VIRUS HAS BEEN DISCOVERED AND HAS INFECTED OVER 1,000,000 PEOPLE" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/new_virus</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/new_virus.html">&lt;p&gt;The Coronavirus is rapidly spreading, with over 126 million cases and
2.76 million deaths. But that is not the virus we should be concerned
about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Four days ago, students at the University of Toronto found an unknown
strain of virus in a young man’s bloodstream. He had been going on about
the anime &lt;em&gt;The Promised Neverland&lt;/em&gt; nonstop. He also had an extremely
high fever, a sore throat, severe pain in his chest and a splitting
headache. Two days later, he fell into a coma, after his sister had told
him that his waifu was not real and passed away twelve hours later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since then, Canadian citizens started showing similar symptoms as
the deceased man. From the research, medical scientists have gathered
that this virus is caused by watching anime, reading manga and/or light
novels, as well as playing anime styled video games. As a result,
victims will gain a sudden obsession of Japanese pop culture. Due to
this, researchers have decided to call this strain of virus “Animeitis”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My daughter has always found anime “geeky” and “childish”. Next thing I
know, she is hooked on the &lt;em&gt;Jojo’s Bizarre Adventure&lt;/em&gt; franchise&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; She
has been binge watching it nonstop,” a tearful mother reports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have also been reports of individuals believing that anime is real
or that they are in an anime. For instance, a woman in Vancouver has
been trying to awaken her “Quirk” to no avail. She has also started
cosplaying as characters from &lt;em&gt;My Hero Academia&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This virus has already infected millions of people across Canada, as
well as a few hundred cases in the States. Many provinces are now in
lockdown, including Ontario, Quebec, Manitoba, British Columbia and
Alberta. President Joe Biden is considering putting the entire U.S. in
lockdown as well. Many world leaders have also put their countries in
lockdown, as they are afraid their own citizens suffer Animeitis as
well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We still have little knowledge on Animeitis, but Ontario’s Ministry of
Health’s President, Iain Stewart, has told us which symptoms to watch
out for, as well as how to prevent the virus from spreading further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The usual symptoms of COVID-19; fatigue, fever, sore throat, diarrhea,
headaches, and difficulty breathing are present. A sudden obsession with
anime, and in worst cases, believing that it is nonfiction are the
symptoms that differentiate Animeitis from the superior virus.” Stewart
says. “As for precautions to take, don’t go outside unless you
absolutely have to. If you do, wear a mask and avoid interacting with
people. Since the virus can spread at a wide range compared to the
coronavirus, stay at least twelve feet away from others instead of only
seven. Wash your hands frequently and sanitize. Avoid touching your
face, eyes, nose and mouth. And most importantly, do not come into
contact with anything anime based.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And if your loved ones have been infected, do &lt;em&gt;not,&lt;/em&gt; under any
circumstances, tell them that anime is not real. This will cause them to
either have a severe heart attack or stroke. All individuals who have
been told this harsh reality have died shortly after,” he reports
gravely. “Instead, have them self-isolate immediately. The recovery
process is the exact same as COVID-19. If we work together, we can
combat Animeitis.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Animeitis is still being researched around the world and a vaccine is
yet to be developed. One major question being asked is if it is possible
for those infected with the virus to become sicker upon being further
exposed to Japanese entertainment, including anime, JMMORPGS, manga,
light novels and J-pop. But rest assured that once infected, cases will
not worsen. All we can do now is pray that we can put an end to this
before it gets out of hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quarantine can be quite boring, so here are some anime series for
victims to stream while they recover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;seraph-of-the-end&quot;&gt;Seraph Of The End&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genres:&lt;/strong&gt; Action, Apocalyptic And Post Apocalyptic Fiction, Dark
Fantasy, Drama, Military, Supernatural, Vampire&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Set in 2012, the world allegedly comes to an end at the
hands of a fatal virus, wiping out most of the human population and
leaving only children under the age of thirteen untouched. It is at this
time that vampires emerge from the shadows of the Earth and take the
surviving children as their food source. Eight years later, a young teen
named Yūichirō Hyakuya joins the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, an
organization dedicated to exterminating vampires, to avenge the deaths
of his orphaned family and reclaim his best friend, Mikaela Hyakuya,
from the vampires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;steinsgate&quot;&gt;Steins;Gate&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genres:&lt;/strong&gt; Comedy, Drama, Psychological Thriller, Science Fiction,
Thriller&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; The series follows Rintaro Okabe, a self proclaimed mad
scientist who works with his roommates on a microwave that can transfer
messages to the future. Without getting captured by an evil
organization, SERN, the group of scientists must work together to stop
SERN’s diabolical plans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tokyo-ghoul&quot;&gt;Tokyo Ghoul&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genres:&lt;/strong&gt; Dark Fantasy, Drama, Horror, Mystery, Psychological
Thriller, Supernatural, Thriller&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; A university student, Ken Kaneki, goes on a date with the
girl of his dreams, Rize Kamishiro, only to discover that she is
actually a ghoul, a man-eating being that lives off human flesh, who
attempts to kill him. By some miracle, Rize dies before she can eat
Kaneki, leaving him in critical condition. When he wakes up in the
hospital, Kaneki discovers that the doctors saved his life by
implementing Rize’s organs in his body, turning him into a half-ghoul.
Horrified by this new reality, Kaneki is taken in by the owner and
employees of Anteiku, a coffee shop run by ghouls, who teach Kaneki how
to deal with his life as a newly turned ghoul.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;haikyuu&quot;&gt;Haikyuu!!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genres:&lt;/strong&gt; Comedy, Coming Of Age, Drama, High School, Sports,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary:&lt;/strong&gt; Shouyou Hinata decides to revive his middle school’s
volleyball team after being inspired by the volleyball legend known as
“Little Giant”. This newly formed team makes it to the tournament, only
to be brutally beaten by Tobio Kageyama, the so-called “King Of The
Court”. Hinata vows to suppress Kageyama. After graduating from middle
school, Hinata joins Karasuno High School’s volleyball team- only to
realize Kageyama is one of his teammates. Due to his short height,
Hinata struggles to find his role in the team, even with his incredible
jumping height. However, he soon comes to realize that Kageyama has his
own problems that only Hinata can help with. As the team spends time
together, they learn they can only be successful if they work together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: The Ryerson Anime Club by Student from
&lt;a href=&quot;https://why.ryerson.ca/the-ryerson-anime-club/&quot;&gt;https://why.ryerson.ca/the-ryerson-anime-club/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>rsyed</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">The Coronavirus is rapidly spreading, with over 126 million cases and 2.76 million deaths. But that is not the virus we should be concerned about.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/anime_club.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/anime_club.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 Ways to Protect Yourself from COVID-19</title><link href="/2021/04/protect_yourself.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 Ways to Protect Yourself from COVID-19" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/protect_yourself</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/protect_yourself.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey MCI. There seems to be a lot of misinformation being spread about
how to keep yourself safe during the pandemic. To combat this, the
journalists at &lt;em&gt;The Bacon&lt;/em&gt; have talked to experts in the field to bring
you the most reliable advice to protect yourself from the novel
coronavirus. Here are our top tips:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drink water:&lt;/strong&gt; Viruses are very bad at swimming and will drown if you
drink enough water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set boundaries:&lt;/strong&gt; Say, “Stop. I don’t feel comfortable with you taking
over my cells. Please respect my personal space.” The virus will be
shocked by your level of maturity and will back down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Throw your wallet in front of you and run in the opposite direction:&lt;/strong&gt;
The virus will go for your wallet and leave you alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use street smarts:&lt;/strong&gt; When face-to-face with the virus, chew a tab of
alka-seltzer. This creates a foaming-at-the-mouth appearance that makes
it look like you have rabies. This will throw the virus off its rhythm.
It won’t know how to fight back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make fun of it:&lt;/strong&gt; We here at &lt;em&gt;The Bacon&lt;/em&gt; are not fans of bullying, but
desperate times call for desperate measures. Say, “Who do you think you
are? You don’t even have cells. You’re only able to reproduce by
leeching off others. How pathetic. Are you even alive?” This will send
the virus into an existential crisis. It will cry. Use this time to make
your escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Become TikTok famous:&lt;/strong&gt; It will be intimidated by your virality and
won’t try to compete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the most up-to-date information we have now. We hope you have
learned something useful. Please continue to listen to health
professionals and follow the guidelines set by your federal and
provincial governments. Stay safe Bears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Source: &lt;em&gt;“People Wearing DIY Masks” by cottonbro from
Pexels&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>srao</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Hey MCI. There seems to be a lot of misinformation being spread about how to keep yourself safe during the pandemic. To combat this, the journalists at The Bacon have talked to experts in the field to bring you the most reliable advice to protect yourself from the novel coronavirus. Here are our top tips:</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/protect_yourself.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/protect_yourself.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">My Quarantine Things</title><link href="/2021/04/quarantine_things.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Quarantine Things" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/quarantine_things</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/quarantine_things.html">&lt;p&gt;Sung in the tune of “My Favourite Things” from &lt;em&gt;The Sound of Music&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going for days without getting some sunlight,&lt;br /&gt;
Staring for hours at screens that are too bright,&lt;br /&gt;
Missing the days we could have band and strings,&lt;br /&gt;
These are a few of my quarantine things&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do we sign in today?” I can’t stop asking,&lt;br /&gt;
At least I can’t forget which class I’m having (I still do),&lt;br /&gt;
Bad wifi during my google meetings,&lt;br /&gt;
These are a few of my quarantine things&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saying I’ll try new things in the beginning,&lt;br /&gt;
One whole year later and I’m still not baking,&lt;br /&gt;
I hope this pandemic has an ending,&lt;br /&gt;
These are a few of my quarantine things&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Changing out of&lt;br /&gt;
Pyjamas is&lt;br /&gt;
Basically self care&lt;br /&gt;
It pains me to say this but some still need help&lt;br /&gt;
Remembering to&lt;br /&gt;
Stay home :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>epark</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Sung in the tune of “My Favourite Things” from The Sound of Music.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/quarantine_things.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/quarantine_things.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 Taylor Swift To Quit Music Forever?</title><link href="/2021/04/taylor_swift.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 Taylor Swift To Quit Music Forever?" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/taylor_swift</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/taylor_swift.html">&lt;p&gt;Many feelings arose when this news developed: Taylor Swift, named “the
music industry” herself, is going to quit music forever. These were
largely feelings of shock, frustration, and confusion, followed by
experiencing all her albums again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noted, there was previously a similar scare in a candid interview with
&lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt;, where Taylor Swift revealed she almost quit making
music. However, this time, sources reveal that this news is real.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“After the sudden and highly welcomed releases of &lt;em&gt;Folklore&lt;/em&gt; and
&lt;em&gt;Evermore&lt;/em&gt;, Taylor Swift is to stop making new music,” revealed a
trusted source. It is predicted that she will be focusing solely on her
re-recordings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although this unexpected announcement is saddening, one can find joy in
looking at the bright side of things. With re-recordings, we can return
to our childhoods, and additionally, hear lyrical masterpieces that were
originally in the “vault” but have made a joyous escape engrossed in
parentheses. Additionally, hardcore Swifties are known to overthink, to
a point where they are counting the amount of spaces Taylor Swift has
put between her captions and if they have any relation to the number 13.
Surprisingly, there is nothing irrational about this practice, as
“easter eggs” are hidden on a consistent and bordering maniacal basis
for this artist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, throughout all of this, disbelief is a feeling that will definitely
be shared. Largely because of the fact that TS13 is yet to be released.
As strange as this may seem to the common folk, it has valid reasoning
behind it. A person who plans for the release dates of her albums to add
up to “13” cannot possibly not have thirteen albums in her discography.
So perhaps, this news is an easter egg within itself. Is someone going
to count the number of letters and the exact second to which this was
posted? However, for some reason, if it is in fact true, manifesting it
to be false is always an option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Image Credit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/58820009@N05/6966861157&quot;&gt;“Taylor Swift”&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/58820009@N05&quot;&gt;Eva Rinaldi Celebrity Photographer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>rmatharu</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Many feelings arose when this news developed: Taylor Swift, named “the music industry” herself, is going to quit music forever. These were largely feelings of shock, frustration, and confusion, followed by experiencing all her albums again.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/taylor_swift.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/taylor_swift.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">🥓 Washrooms Cancelled At MCI</title><link href="/2021/04/washrooms_cancelled.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🥓 Washrooms Cancelled At MCI" /><published>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-04-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/04/washrooms_cancelled</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/04/washrooms_cancelled.html">&lt;p&gt;MCI students have changed much of their school life to combat the
Covid-19 virus. We have to wear masks, socially distance, and use the
quadmester system, if we are going to school at all. However, we still
have the luxury of using the amazing Martingrove washrooms, a luxury
that we may also have to give up. In a secret meeting with Beacon staff,
the administration at our school revealed their plans to ban the use of
our bathrooms, mandating instead MCI Bear diapers for all students.
We’ve decided to break the news to the public, as this is a great blow
to our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, we must take all measures necessary to combat this pandemic.
If that means wearing diapers, then so be it. We recognize that this may
be a change, but honestly, it is a return to a simpler time. Just 14
years ago, most Martingrove students would have been walking around with
a diaper anyway, so this might be just the change we need to be more
comfortable at school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not only for in person students though. Because Martingrove aims
to be inclusive and incorporate everyone into our community, the school
has decided that virtual students will also partake in this diaper
wearing. This is to unite the students and have us all feel the bear
spirit. All students can pick up their Bear Diaper at the main office on
Monday and Tuesday. Remember, we’re all in this together!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is part of “The Bacon” - The Beacon’s April Fools’ edition. We hope you enjoyed!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>eca</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">MCI students have changed much of their school life to combat the Covid-19 virus. We have to wear masks, socially distance, and use the quadmester system, if we are going to school at all. However, we still have the luxury of using the amazing Martingrove washrooms, a luxury that we may also have to give up. In a secret meeting with Beacon staff, the administration at our school revealed their plans to ban the use of our bathrooms, mandating instead MCI Bear diapers for all students. We’ve decided to break the news to the public, as this is a great blow to our community.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/washrooms_cancelled.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/washrooms_cancelled.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Graviton: Future Fuel</title><link href="/2021/03/TheGraviton-FutureFuel.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Graviton: Future Fuel" /><published>2021-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/TheGraviton-FutureFuel</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/TheGraviton-FutureFuel.html">&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been filling the tank to your new spaceship and thought,
“I wish there was a better way to power the engine.” Enter the Graviton!
With its subatomic superpower, its potential applications are
unimaginable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To understand the graviton, we must first understand a bit of quantum
mechanics. The main principle is that everything is made of quanta – or
packets – of energy and these quanta behave as both particles and waves.
Take visible light, for example, which is composed of packets of
electromagnetic energy, or photons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are four fundamental forces in the universe: gravity,
electromagnetic force, weak and strong nuclear forces. All of these,
except for gravity, have been proven to follow the laws of quantum
mechanics. This means they have specific subatomic “exchange particles”
that interact with other particles to cause these forces.
Electromagnetic force is caused by the photon. Strong nuclear force is
traceable to the gluon. Weak nuclear force is transmitted by the
movement of W and Z bosons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowing this, scientists predict that the elementary particle which
causes apples to fall onto our heads and shooting stars to traverse the
night, is the graviton! If this mysterious particle exists, it is
expected to have no mass, no charge, and travel at the speed of light,
similar to a photon. Though still considered theoretical, physicists
like Zvi Bern continuously challenge themselves to calculate the
behaviours of this particle with increasing precision, which involves
taking on new perspectives of the universe – even one where space-time
is an illusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if it fits with quantum mechanics and scientists can already predict
its properties, why hasn’t the graviton been proven to exist yet? For
one, gravity is extremely weak, and as physicist Freeman Dyson once
stated, the detector needed to prove the graviton’s existence would have
to be so massive it would “collapse into a black hole.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there is an even larger factor that has plagued the physics
world for nearly a century: the struggle to unify Einstein’s Theory of
General Relativity with quantum theory. Both have vastly different views
on gravity. While Einstein’s theory states gravity is an attractive
force as the result of matter distorting space-time, quantum theory
views gravity as being caused by the transferring of gravitons between
particles. Merging these two theories – and proving it – has been a
complex task for physicists, giving rise to fascinating hypotheses from
String Theory to pulling an Interstellar and falling into a black hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is only a matter of time until the existence of the graviton – or its
future equivalent – is proven. When it is, it will help us create
numerous mind-bending applications! The most intriguing being an
entirely new way to fuel transportation. By harnessing a way to
manipulate the graviton, just as we manipulate the emission of photons
to create light, gravity can be used for future space travels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, we can facilitate more efficient spacecraft propulsion. By
manipulating an area near a rocket to have a higher concentration of
gravitons, we can increase that area’s gravity, pulling the rocket
towards this increased gravitational zone. This would work the same as
when a spaceship loops around a planet to take advantage of its
gravitational field and increase its velocity. Now, instead of needing
fuel to accelerate a spaceship, we can use gravity to our advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An even more ambitious application: creating our own wormhole to another
part of the universe! By greatly increasing the concentration of
gravitons in a certain area, we could succeed in curving space-time to
create a shortcut to a different part of space – or even time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For now these are all just speculations. However, it is important to
remember that scientific progress has evolved exponentially. Just over
100 years ago, it was thought that neutrons and protons were the
smallest particles to exist. Yet, the discovery of quarks and even more
fundamental particles have unveiled another layer in our quest to
discover the ultimate fabric of the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although we may only be at the beginning of our journey of learning how
the universe works, that doesn’t keep us from searching further. We must
continue laying the foundations for our future discoveries, ceaselessly
reviving the world of science.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>dbrebeanu</name></author><category term="articles" /><summary type="html">Have you ever been filling the tank to your new spaceship and thought, “I wish there was a better way to power the engine.” Enter the Graviton! With its subatomic superpower, its potential applications are unimaginable.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/TheGraviton.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/TheGraviton.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>